
--- javascript:S6853 ---
src/components/TAG/OfferLetters/OfferLetterForm.js:
  Line 496: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 507: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 518: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 529: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 544: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 554: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 573: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 584: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 594: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 607: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 617: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 628: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 654: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 665: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 674: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 687: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 696: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 705: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 723: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 734: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 745: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 756: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 768: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 781: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 793: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 803: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 813: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 839: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 861: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 879: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 892: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 905: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 915: A form label must be associated with a control.
src/components/TAG/OfferLetters/OfferLetterPreviewPage.js:
  Line 235: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 244: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 254: A form label must be associated with a control.
src/components/TAG/OfferLetters/OfferLettersDashboard.js:
  Line 289: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 300: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 312: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 324: A form label must be associated with a control.
src/components/HR/RegisterCandidate.js:
  Line 432: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 451: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 472: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 366: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 197: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 312: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 337: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 408: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 300: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 216: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 225: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 237: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 247: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 260: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 275: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 286: A form label must be associated with a control.
src/components/Auth/Login.js:
  Line 281: A form label must be associated with a control.
src/components/HR/HRReview.js:
  Line 288: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 239: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 256: A form label must be associated with a control.
src/components/Forms/OnboardingForm.js:
  Line 1374: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 292: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 300: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 322: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 337: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 349: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 367: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 379: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 506: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 514: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 522: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 532: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 540: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 550: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 560: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 582: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 464: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 789: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 646: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 654: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 666: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 681: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 694: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 708: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 720: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 814: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 820: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 829: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 840: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 961: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 423: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 431: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 440: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 242: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 415: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 763: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 628: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 636: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 753: A form label must be associated with a control.
src/components/HR/DocumentExpiry.js:
  Line 395: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 409: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 429: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 438: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 449: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 457: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 468: A form label must be associated with a control.
src/components/HR/ReferenceCheck.js:
  Line 268: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 282: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 299: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 308: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 321: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 330: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 341: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 349: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 366: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 516: A form label must be associated with a control.
  Line 529: A form label must be associated with a control.

--- javascript:S6848 ---
src/components/TAG/OfferLetters/OfferLettersDashboard.js:
  Line 418: Avoid non-native interactive elements. If using native HTML is not possible, add an appropriate role and support for tabbing, mouse, keyboard, and touch inputs to an interactive content element.
src/components/HR/HRReview.js:
  Line 212: Avoid non-native interactive elements. If using native HTML is not possible, add an appropriate role and support for tabbing, mouse, keyboard, and touch inputs to an interactive content element.
  Line 282: Avoid non-native interactive elements. If using native HTML is not possible, add an appropriate role and support for tabbing, mouse, keyboard, and touch inputs to an interactive content element.
  Line 283: Avoid non-native interactive elements. If using native HTML is not possible, add an appropriate role and support for tabbing, mouse, keyboard, and touch inputs to an interactive content element.
  Line 234: Avoid non-native interactive elements. If using native HTML is not possible, add an appropriate role and support for tabbing, mouse, keyboard, and touch inputs to an interactive content element.
  Line 235: Avoid non-native interactive elements. If using native HTML is not possible, add an appropriate role and support for tabbing, mouse, keyboard, and touch inputs to an interactive content element.
src/components/Validation/Validation.js:
  Line 155: Avoid non-native interactive elements. If using native HTML is not possible, add an appropriate role and support for tabbing, mouse, keyboard, and touch inputs to an interactive content element.
src/components/Layout/Header.js:
  Line 185: Avoid non-native interactive elements. If using native HTML is not possible, add an appropriate role and support for tabbing, mouse, keyboard, and touch inputs to an interactive content element.
src/components/UI/ContextualHelp.js:
  Line 58: Avoid non-native interactive elements. If using native HTML is not possible, add an appropriate role and support for tabbing, mouse, keyboard, and touch inputs to an interactive content element.
  Line 70: Avoid non-native interactive elements. If using native HTML is not possible, add an appropriate role and support for tabbing, mouse, keyboard, and touch inputs to an interactive content element.
src/components/UI/Tooltip.js:
  Line 44: Avoid non-native interactive elements. If using native HTML is not possible, add an appropriate role and support for tabbing, mouse, keyboard, and touch inputs to an interactive content element.
src/components/HR/HRChat.js:
  Line 232: Avoid non-native interactive elements. If using native HTML is not possible, add an appropriate role and support for tabbing, mouse, keyboard, and touch inputs to an interactive content element.
src/components/HR/HRCandidateWorkflow.js:
  Line 180: Avoid non-native interactive elements. If using native HTML is not possible, add an appropriate role and support for tabbing, mouse, keyboard, and touch inputs to an interactive content element.
src/components/Chat/ChatWidget.js:
  Line 38: Avoid non-native interactive elements. If using native HTML is not possible, add an appropriate role and support for tabbing, mouse, keyboard, and touch inputs to an interactive content element.
  Line 48: Avoid non-native interactive elements. If using native HTML is not possible, add an appropriate role and support for tabbing, mouse, keyboard, and touch inputs to an interactive content element.
src/components/Layout/Sidebar.js:
  Line 132: Avoid non-native interactive elements. If using native HTML is not possible, add an appropriate role and support for tabbing, mouse, keyboard, and touch inputs to an interactive content element.
src/components/UI/Modal.js:
  Line 19: Avoid non-native interactive elements. If using native HTML is not possible, add an appropriate role and support for tabbing, mouse, keyboard, and touch inputs to an interactive content element.
  Line 20: Avoid non-native interactive elements. If using native HTML is not possible, add an appropriate role and support for tabbing, mouse, keyboard, and touch inputs to an interactive content element.

--- css:S7924 ---
src/components/TAG/OfferLetters/OfferLetterForm.css:
  Line 39: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
  Line 49: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
  Line 134: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
  Line 316: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
  Line 395: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
  Line 411: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
  Line 417: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
  Line 452: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
src/components/TAG/OfferLetters/OfferLetterPreviewPage.css:
  Line 184: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
  Line 189: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
  Line 195: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
src/components/TAG/OfferLetters/OfferLettersDashboard.css:
  Line 70: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
  Line 136: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
  Line 141: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
  Line 146: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
  Line 382: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
  Line 442: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
  Line 461: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
src/components/Auth/Login.css:
  Line 167: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
src/components/UI/EnhancedProgressBar.css:
  Line 88: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
src/components/HR/DocumentExpiry.css:
  Line 60: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
  Line 297: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
src/components/Layout/Sidebar.css:
  Line 142: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
  Line 116: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
  Line 121: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
src/components/HR/AuditLog.css:
  Line 109: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
src/components/HR/HRAnalytics.css:
  Line 96: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
  Line 101: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
src/components/HR/HRCandidateWorkflow.css:
  Line 209: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
  Line 214: Text does not meet the minimal contrast requirement with its background.
